आपारे लिवारा लिवारे लिवारे लिवारे लिवारे लिवारे लिवारे लिवारे लिवारे लिवारे लिवारे लिवारे लिवारे लिवारे लिवारे लिवारे लिवारे लिवारे लिवारे लिवारे लिवारे लिवारे लिवारे लिवारे लिवारे लिवारे लिवारे
自由主义的liba天秤座天秤座天秤座天秤座利瓦拉·利瓦拉·利瓦拉（liwara liwara）
I'm facing two, I'm facing two, I'm facing two, I'm facing two.
我面对两个，我面对两个，我面对两个，我面对两个。
Nosotros nos vemos en la próxima, nos vemos en la próxima, nos vemos en la próxima.
Thank you for having me.
接下来再见，接下来再见，在下一个中见。
谢谢你有我。
I'm gonna do this. I'm gonna do this. I'm gonna do this.
我要这样做。我要这样做。我要这样做。
Wanna listen to these live shows here at the world I wonder when?
想在世界上听这些现场表演，我想知道什么时候？
I'm going to run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run
I'm going to run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run,run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run
Thank you all for watching.
谢谢大家的观看。